Conservative Party of New York State; Records apap060
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1962-1986; 7; 15 cubic ft.
  - Federal Legislation, 1974; 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Federal Register, 1972 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Federation of Greater New York Rifle & Pistol Clubs, Inc., 1975-1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Ferraro, Geraldine, 1983; 1985 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Field, Floyd Bennett, 1971 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Films, Informational, 1965-1966; 1972 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Financial Management Associates, Inc., 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Fino, Paul A., 1964; 1966 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Firearms, 1975 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Fire Department, 1976-1977; 1980-1982 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Firefighters, 1976; 1978-1979 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - First Amendment, Undated (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - First Monday, 1976 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Fiscal Observer, The, 1977 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Fiscal Policy -- New York State -- Folder 1, 1963-1970 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Fiscal Policy -- New York State -- Folder 2, 1964-1968 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Fiscal Policy -- New York State -- Folder 3, 1970-1973 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Fiscal Policy -- New York State -- Folder 4, 1970-1973 (Box 9 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Fiscal Policy -- U.S., 1962-1972; 3 folders (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Fish, Hamilton, Jr., 1970; 1972; 1980; 1982 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Flack, John T., 1970; 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Flag of the United States, 1963; 1966-1967; 1969; 1971 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Flat Tax, 1982 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Fleischmann Commission Report of Public School Financing in New York State, 1972-1973 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Flinn, Robert S. (Mrs), 1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Florida, 1974-1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Florida Perspective, Florida Conservative Union,Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Fluoridation, 1963-1967; 1971; 1975; 1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Flying Saucers, ca. 1966 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Fonda, Jane, 1972; 1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Food Stamp Program, 1975-1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - "For America", 1978 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Ford Foundation, 1972; 1974; 1975 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1975-1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Fordham University, 1973; 1976; 1980-1983 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Foreign Aid, 1963-1967; 1979-1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Foreign Countries, 1974 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Foreign Policy, 1961-1967; 1976-1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Foreman, Con. Edward, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Forest Hills Housing Project, 1971-1972 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Former Police Officers, 1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Forms, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Fortas, Abe, 1965; 1968 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Forum, 1963 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Foster Care, 1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, Inc. (FEE), 1974 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Foundation of Law & Society, 1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - France, 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Free China, 1974; 1977; 1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Free Congress Foundation: The Political Report, 1978 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Free Congress Research & Education Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Free Press International, 1981 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Free Society, The, 1965-1966 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Free Trade, 1959 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Freedom, 1975; 1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Freedom Activity, 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Freedom -- Communism, 1969 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Free Enterprise, 1962 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Freedom House, 1965 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Freedom Party, 1962 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Freedom School, 1962 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Friedlander, Miriam, 1961; 1963; 1966; 1970; 1973 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Friedman, Milton, 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Friends of St. Johns, 1976 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Fuchsberg, Jacob D., 1974 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Fu-Jen University, 1974 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Full Assessment (property taxes -- NYC), 197[9] (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Full Crew Laws, 1965 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Fulton, Rev. Robert (Neighborhood Church, Greenwich Village), Undated (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Fund for a Conservative Majority, 1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Fund for Life, Inc., 1975 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Fund Raising -- Sample Literature, 1968; 1971-1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Fund Raising -- Sample Literature, 1974-1977 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Fund Raising -- Sample Literature, 1978 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Fund Raising -- Sample Literature, 1979 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Fund Raising -- Sample Literature, 1980 (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Fund Raising -- U.S. Congressional Advisory Board, Undated (Box 10 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Gabrielli, Domenick L., 1972; 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Gallagher, Jack and Jayne, 1972; 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Gallagher, John T., 1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Galligan, Tom, 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Galvao, Henrique M., 1963 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Galvin, Thomas, 1973-1974; 1976-1977 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Galvin, Thomas -- Press Releases, 1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Gambling, 1976-1981 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Gary, Gayle, ca. 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Gateway National Park, 1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Gavin, William, 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Gay Rights, 1974-1978; 1981; 1985-1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Gay Rights Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Gegan, Joseph F., 1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Genocide Treaty, 1977 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Germany, 1976; 1978 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Gibson, James, 1969 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - God's Workshop, 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Gold, 1961-1965; 1975; 1981 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1962-1966; 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Goldwater, Barry -- Campaign Newsletter, 1964 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Goldwater, Barry -- Primaries and Delegates -- Folder 1, 1965 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Goodell, Charles, 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Gottfried, Richard N. -- Mild Deregulation, 1981 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Government Finances, 1978-1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Government Subsidation of Food, 1963 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Grain Sales to the Soviet Union, 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Grand Juries, 1974; 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Green, Bill, [1979] (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Green, Mark, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Green Revolution, 1972-1973; 1977 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Groezinger, Robert, 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Guardian Angels, 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Guile, Norman, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Gun Control, 1965; 1968; 1974-1976; 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Gunning, Rosemary, Undated (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Gurney Amendment (re: North Vietnam), 1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Haggerty, John F., 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Haig, Alexander M., Jr., 1980-1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Halpern, Seymour, ca. 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Hampton, Mason L., Jr., 1966-1967; 1969; 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Harnett, Joel, ca. 1978 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Harris, Fred Roy, 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Harris-Stafford Bill, 1973 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Hatch Act, 1977; 1981 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Hatch, Orrin, 1978 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Hawaii, 1971 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Health Care, 1976-1977; 1979-1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Hearst, Patty, 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Heckman, Robert, ca. 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Helms, Jesse, 1975-1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Helsinki Trip of President Ford, 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Hentel, Nat H., ca. 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Highway Authority -- New Jersey, 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Highways, 1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Hillsdale College, 1975-1978 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Hintz, Julius H., 1974 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Hirschfield, Abraham, 1974; 1976-1977; 1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Hispanic Committee, 1971 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Hispanics, 1971-1972; 1977 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Hiss, Alger, 1962; 1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Hoguet, Rene \e, 1967-1968 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth, 1979-1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Homosexuality, 1971-1977; 1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Homosexuality -- Legislation, 1974-1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Hongisto, Richard, 1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1971-1972 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Hospitals, 1965; 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - House Committee on Un - American Activities, ca. 1965 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Howard Allen Enterprises, Inc., 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Human Events, 1962-1964; 1975-1976; 1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Human Events, 1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Human Life Foundation, Inc., 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Human Rights, 1979 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1968 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Hurd, Bradley J., 1974; 1976 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Hurley Report, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Hurwitz, Howard L., 1972-1977; 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Idaho, 1965; 1974; 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Ideas: A Journal of Contemporary Jewish Thought, 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Illegal Aliens, 1977-1980; 1982; 1987 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Illinois, 1965; 1971-1972; 1974-1975; 1977; 1980 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Immigrants, 1980; 1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Immigration, 1984 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Imprimis, 1976-1980; 1982 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Incredible Bread Machine, The -- Book and Movie, 1975 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - Independent Bar Association, 1962-1965 (Box 11 (7-Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - Independence Party, 1975 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - India, 1963 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Indiana, 1971; 1974-1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Individual Rights, 1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Indonesia, 1963-1965; 1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Inflation, 1974; 1978-1980 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1978-1981 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Insanity Defense, 1978 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1975 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Insurance Legislation, 1978-1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Integration of Schools, 1964-1965 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Intelligence, 1977-1981 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, Inc., 1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Intern Program, New York State Assembly, 1971 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Internal Security, 1974 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - International Digest, 1974; 1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - International Moneyline, 1975 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - International Platform Committee, 1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - International Security, 1958 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - International Women's Year, 1976-1977 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - International Youth Federation for Freedom, 1965 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Invitations -- Samples, 1979-1980 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Iowa, 1975-1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Iran, 1979-1981 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Ireland, 1979; 1981 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Issues for Action -- The Smithkline Forum for a Healthier American Society, 1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Javits, Jacob, 1980 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Javits, Jacob -- Research from Americans for Constitutional Action, 1963-1968; 2 folders (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Jefferson County, 1973; 1976-1977 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - John Birch Society, 1962-1967; 1974-1975 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Kavanagh, Thomas J. re: Democratic corruption in NYC as evidenced in Rohrbach vs. Coven Suit, 1985-1986 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Kay, John Andrew, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Keating, Barbara -- U.S. Senate Campaign, 1974 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Kemp, Con. Jack, 1982; 1986 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Korea, 1965; 1977; 1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Koreagate, 1977; 1980 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Kram, Shirley Wohl, 1983 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Krebiozen, 1963 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Krupsak, Mary Anne, ca. 1974 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Kudlow, Lawrence A., ca. 1982 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Kunzeman, Joseph J., 1967 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Labor, 1962-1967; 1970-1980; 3 folders (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43-45)
  - Labor, 1978; 1982 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Labor Party -- U.S., 1975; 1977 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Labor Reform Bill, 1978 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Lane, Clarence "Larry" -- Homeowner's Guide, ca. 1980 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Lasky, Victor, 1979 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Law Committee, 1961; 1963; 1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Law Enforcement, 1964; 1972-1973; 1979-1980; 1983 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - LeBoutillier, Con. John, 1980-1982 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Leff, James J. -- Campaign Chief Judge, 1973 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Legal Case re: Board of Elections, Undated (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Legal Cases, 1971-1972 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Legality -- NYS Election Law, 1971 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Legislative Pamphlet: "Know Who Represents You in 19[ ]", 1971-1981 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Lehrman, Lewis, 1979; 1982; 1985 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Liberal Party, 1962; 1976 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Libertarian Party, 1972; 1974-1976; 1980; 1982 (Box 12 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Liberty Amendment, 1963-1966 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Liberty Lobby, 1968; 1973-1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Lindsay, John, 1964; 1972 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Lipke, Dr. Ken, 1983 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Lobbyists, 1972 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Loeb, John L., 1980-1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Long Island, 1975; 1977; 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Long Island Conservative (newsletter), 1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - L.I. Parkway Police Shield (newsletter), 1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Long, Michael R., 1980; 1983; 1986; 1988 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Longo, Nicholas A., 1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - "Look-Say" Reading Method, 1963 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Louisiana, 1974-1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1960-1966 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Lugar, Richard, 1978; 1980-1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Mail Registration -- Voter, 1975-1976; 1978 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Maine, 1971; 1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Malta, 1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Maltese, Andrew, 1988 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Maltese, Serphin R., [ ], 1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Mandates -- Federal, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Mandatory Student Activity Fees, 1975-1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Manes, Donald R., 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Manhattan Right to Life Committee, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Manion, 1962; 1973-1974 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Manuals -- Other Organizations, 1960-1964 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Maps of NYS, Undated (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Marano, Luigi R., 1964 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Marchi, John, 1969; 1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Marchi for Mayor -- Sublease with Fordham University, 1969 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Maryland, 1972-1977; 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Maryland Conservative Union, 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Mason, Edwyn E. (State Assembly), 1968; 1970; 1972 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Massachusetts, 1974-1975; 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Massachusetts Conservative Party, 1972; 1975; 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Mass Transit, 1963; 1965-1969; 1971; 1974-1976; 1978-1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Master, Daniel L., 1974 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - McGrath, Diane, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Media, 1985-1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Medicaid, 1966 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    See Clippings File--Medicaid.
  - Meier, William G., 1972 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Merchant Marine Defense Commission, 1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - M.I.A.s, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Missing Children Bill -- NYS Assembly Votes, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Morality for Media, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Moran, Emerson -- columnist, 1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Motto: CPNYS, 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Muratori, Jack, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - N.A.A.C.P. -- Legal Defense Fund, Undated (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1972-1973; 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Narcotics, 1963-1972 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Nassau County, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Nathan Hale Conservative Club, 1976; 1981-1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - National Affairs -- VFW, 1978 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - National Alliance, Undated (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1966-1968 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - National Citizens' Committee for Fairness to the Presidency, 1974 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - National Committee against U.S. Recognition of Communist Vietnam, 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1967 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - National Committee for Responsible Patriotism, Inc., 1968; 1972; 1978 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - National Conservative Party, 1972; 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - National Conservative Political Action Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - National Council for Civic Responsibility, 1964-1965 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - NBC -- 1980 Moscow Olympics, 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - National Organization of Italian-American Women, 1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - New Jersey -- Editorials, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - NLRB Case Handling Manual (NLRB -- National Labor Relations Board), 1982 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - New Right Report, The, 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - N.Y.C., Association of the Bar of: Report of Committee of the Judiciary, 1967 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - N.Y.C. Budget, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - N.Y.C. Census (editorial), 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - N.Y.C. Conservative Party, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - N.Y.C. Debt Moratorium, 1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - N.Y.C. "Enterprise Zones", 1979 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - N.Y.C. Mayoral Race, 1977 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - N.Y.C. Mayoral Race, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - N.Y.C. -- Mayor's Task on the Constitutional Convention, On the Report on, 1967 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - New York Industry -- Labor Committee for Resource Recovery (re: Deposit Bottles), 1975 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - NYPIRG (New York Public Interest Research Group, Inc., 1986 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - NYS Board of Elections -- 1980 Election Results (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - NYS Budget, 1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - NYS Coalition for Legislative Reform, 1973 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - NYS Comptroller -- Edward V. Regan, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - N.Y.S.C.P., 1981 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - N.Y.S.C.P. -- Peace Through Strength Initiative, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - NYS Conservative Political Association, 1961-1962 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - NYS Constitution, 1966-1967; 1975-1976 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 88)
  - NYS Constitutional Amendments, 1971 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 89)
  - NYS Constitutional Convention, 1965 (Box 13 (7-Subject Files), Folder 90)